Unuefe Ejovwokoghene

Web Developer

Python Django developer with 2 years exploiting model-template-view architectural pattern of Django framework to shorten development times and reduce design costs. Specializes in creating accessible, data-driven web assets. Keen to apply expansive development knowledge to deliver fast. To seek and maintain a full-time position that offers professional challenges utilizing interpersonal skills, excellent time management and problem-solving skills. Friendly student available for weekend, evening and holiday shifts. Considered hardworking, punctual and driven.

Part of a startup company that specializes on online shopping of embedded components, tools needed for drone projects etc.

Work History

2021-05 -Current

Python Developer

Oghenemaega Moses-Johnson, warri, Delta

- Worked independently to design, develop and test code for Futlink Hardware.
- Applied change control best practices to Django development processes to provide software enhancements without disruptions for end users.
- Collaborated with quality assurance team to verify correct implementation of all software development changes.
- Quickly learned new skills and applied them to daily tasks, improving efficiency and productivity.

2020-08 -Current

Startup Founder

Unuefe Ejovwoke, warri, Delta

- Developed key operational initiatives to drive and maintain substantial business growth.
- Cultivated forward-thinking, inclusive and performance-oriented business culture to lead industry in innovation and push progress.
- Created organization's mission and vision statements for use by all employees.
- Developed innovative sales and marketing strategies to facilitate business expansion.

Education

2016-11 -Current

Bachelor of Science: Electrical, Electronics Engineering

Federal University of Petroleum Resources Effurun -Delta State, Effurun

2021-07 -2021-11 Certificate of Course Completion: Mobile Web Specialist

Google Africa Developer Training Program - Online

2021-07 -

Certificate of Jobberman Soft-skillTraining:

2021-07 Soft-skill Training

Certifications

2021-06 Google Africa developer training program

Jobberman Soft Skill Training - Online

2021-07 Jobberman Soft-skill Training

Interests

Graphics designing, video editing and fitness enthusiast

Contact

Address

Warri, Delta, 330105

Phone

09075254818

F-mall

vuwill7114@gmail.com

Skills

Python



Python Django



REST



Web Design

Front End Web Development

Programming

Website optimization

CSS

HTML

Software

Microsoft website editors



Very Good